Contact

slwilso6@asu.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-wilson-53ab8678 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Patient Safety

Languages English

Stephanie Wilson

BSN, RN, CCRN

Phoenix, Arizona

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the CVICU. Skilled in Post-Op Open Heart Recovery, Mechanical Circulatory Support, and ECMO. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing focused on providing evidence-based, patient-centered care.

Experience

Banner - University Medical Center CVICU Registered Nurse June 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Phoenix, Arizona

Arizona Heart Hospital
Registered Nurse
February 2015 - September 2019 (4 years 8 months)
CVICU

Mayo Clinic Registered Nurse January 2018 - June 2018 (6 months) Phoenix, Arizona

Education

University of Arizona

Doctor of Nursing Practice, AGACNP · (2018 - 2020)

Arizona State University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2011 - 2014)